let gameQuestions = [
    {
        question: "What's the name of the founder of Super Mario?", 
        1: "Shigefumi Hino",
        2: "Koji Kondo",
        3: "Shigeru Miyamoto",
        4: "Saturo Okada",
        rightAnswer: "3",
    },
    {
        question: "When was the Gameboy launched in Europe?",
        1: "1990",
        2: "1992",
        3: "1989",
        4: "1991",
        rightAnswer: "1",
    },
    {
        
        question: "What's the name of the main protagonist in the Legend of Zelda-franchise?",
        1: "Zelda",
        2: "Navi",
        3: "Zora",
        4: "Link",
        rightAnswer: "4",
    },
    {
        question: "What's the name of Sonic the Hedgehogs fox friend?",
        1: "Tails",
        2: "Knuckles",
        3: "Rosy",
        4: "Silver",

        rightAnswer: "1",
    },
    {
        question: "Which game has sold the most copies up to date?",
        1: "Minecraft",
        2: "Tetris",
        3: "Wii Sports",
        4: "Super Mario bros 3",

        rightAnswer: "1",
    },
    {
        question: "How many Pok√©mon were there originally?",
        1: "100",
        2: "150",
        3: "125",
        4: "200",

        rightAnswer: "2",
    },
    {
        question: "Who wrote the main theme for The Legend of Zelda?",
        1: "Jeremy Soule",
        2: "Harry Gregson-Wiliams",
        3: "Koji Kondo",
        4: "Yoko Shimomura",

        rightAnswer: "3",
    },
    {
        question: "In which Final Fantasy - game is the main characters' name Claude?",
        1: "X",
        2: "VII",
        3: "III",
        4: "V",

        rightAnswer: "2",
    },
    {
        question: "What was Nintendo's original business?",
        1: "Cameras",
        2: "Electronics",
        3: "Video Games",
        4: "Playing Cards",

        rightAnswer: "4",
    },
    {
        question: "What kind of animal is Yoshi?",
        1: "Monkey",
        2: "Dinosaur",
        3: "Fox",
        4: "Raccoon",

        rightAnswer: "2",
    },

];